[
    {
        "question": "What is the uptime for tier II datacenter?",
         "option1": "0.99749",
         "option2": "0.99982",
         "option3": "0.99995",
         "option4": "0.99671",
         "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many writing scripts of the world are currently supported by Unicode:",
         "option1": "25",
         "option2": "135",
         "option3": "100",
         "option4": "75",
         "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which agency gives datacenter cooling guidelines?",
         "option1": "WHO",
         "option2": "NASA",
         "option3": "Uptime Institute",
         "option4": "ASHRAE  ",
         "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following statements describes shareware?",
         "option1": "Totally free software that is available only on the Internet",
         "option2": "Commercial based software that must be paid for",
         "option3": "Software available for free on a trial basis after which payment will be required  ",
         "option4": "Copyright free software that allows unlimited copies and distribution",
         "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following is an input/output port?",
         "option1": "Linear",
         "option2": "Radial",
         "option3": "Lateral",
         "option4": "FireWire  ",
         "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What O/S does SAP HANA run on?",
         "option1": "RHEL and SLES ",
         "option2": "Windows",
         "option3": "AIX",
         "option4": "HP-UX",
         "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following is a method of publishing frequently updated content such as news headlines online?",
         "option1": "A blog",
         "option2": "RSS  ",
         "option3": "A podcast.",
         "option4": "Instant messaging",
         "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following statements about an End User License Agreement is true?",
         "option1": "It gives full ownership of the software to the user of the software",
         "option2": "It gives the user the exclusive right to copy and sell the software to other potential users",
         "option3": "It gives the user the right to modify the software",
         "option4": "It gives the user the right to install and run the software on a specified number of computers  ",
         "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Oracle IMDB?",
         "option1": "Oracle Inter-Memory Database",
         "option2": "Oracle Intra-Memory Database",
         "option3": "Oracle In-Memory Database  ",
         "option4": "None of the above",
         "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does RSI in computer term stand for?",
         "option1": "Repeated Strain Inclusion",
         "option2": "Regular Systems Initiation",
         "option3": "Routine Structures Infection",
         "option4": "Repetitive Strain Injury  ",
         "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following is a term for an audio or video recording posted on a web site that can be downloaded and played later?",
         "option1": "Podcast  ",
         "option2": "Blog",
         "option3": "VoIP",
         "option4": "RSS Feed",
         "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "The relatively newer '_aaS' in cloud computing is:",
         "option1": "IaaS",
         "option2": "PaaS",
         "option3": "BioAaaS  ",
         "option4": "SaaS",
         "answer": "3"
    }
]